

## Ali Navidi Sari, Iran → +989339668289 2 years of experience ali\_navidi24@yahoo.com Portfolio: westernal.me/

Blog: dev.to/westernal

westernal ali-navidi-850a80209 to westernal

ali-navidi 🖹

A highly motivated 4-year BSc. Computer Engineering student interested in frontend web developing with high team-working and punctuality ability eager to further knowledge and experience with professionals in the related field.

Skills: (Next.js) HTML CSS SEO Git C React.js JavaScript TypeScript Node.js Cypress Express.js MongoDB **Bootstrap** Svelte Remix Java Python **Tailwind** GraphQL

## Experience

Restarone Solutions Inc. restarone.com

Sep 2022 to Dec 2022

Frontend Engineer Toronto, Canada

Jan 2020 to Nov 2021

Frontend developer Tehran, Iran

**Projects** 

social-media-frontend

Oben Origin co.

# www.westernal.net/ github.com/westernal/social-media-frontend

Westernal: a full stack social media based on songs

CSS, JavaScript, Cypress, Next.js

social-media-backend

Westernal: a full stack social media

JavaScript, Express.js, MongoDB, Node.js

Cinema

github.com/westernal/Cinema

 $Watching \ and \ downloading \ movies \ website \ and \ progressive \ web \ app \ (PWA) \ with \ Next. JS \ and \ TypeScript$ 

TypeScript, CSS, JavaScript, Next.js

sari-sartel

sari-sartel.com/ github.com/westernal/sari-sartel

Sari-sartel: a mobile and accessories shop.

JavaScript, CSS, Next.js

Dashboard

dashoard.vercel.app/ github.com/westernal/Dashoard

Admin dashboard using Next JS

JavaScript, CSS, Next.js

Education

Noshiravni University of Technology nit.ac.ir Bachelor's of Science, Computer Engineering Oct 2018 to Feb 2023

**Publications** 

Introducing Westernal: A social media based on songs

**DEV Community** 

 $\label{eq:condition} \begin{tabular}{l} \textcircled{$\mathfrak{p}$ dev.to/westernal/introducing-westernal-a-social-media-based-on-songs-1pa9} \end{tabular}$ 

How do you write your CSS?

DEV Community

dev.to/westernal/how-do-you-write-your-css-3pg2

Languages

Farsi Native

English Advanced

Certificates

React JS- Complete Guide for Frontend Web Development

Udemy

 $Git\ and\ Git\ Hub\ Master\ Class:\ Git\ Workflow,\ Commands\ \&\ Git\ Hub$ 

Udemy

## Bootstrap 4 Bootcamp for Web Development

Udemy